(Bernadette:)So I was taking a shower
this morning and when I got out...
(Bernadette:)...I started to dry off
with what I thought was a towel...
(Bernadette:)...but turned out to be
Howard's mom's underwear.
(Bernadette:)I had to take another shower.
(Bernadette:)It wasn't enough.
(Bernadette:)Nothing will ever be enough.
(Amy:)I once looked in Sheldon's
underwear drawer. He yelled at me.
(Amy:)But now I know what it looks like,
and he can never take that away.
- There's a book under here.
- Oh. I'll get that.
- I got it. I got it.
- No, no, it's okay.
(Bernadette:)- Why do you have a history textbook?
- No, it's... It's not a big deal.
(Penny:)Just taking a class
at the Pasadena Community College.
(Bernadette:)That's great. I didn't know
you wanted to go back to school.
(Penny:)It's just one history class.
(Penny:)Look, I didn't finish college,
so I thought I would give it a try.
(Amy:)Not to mention your acting career
is going south like Sherman.